Finding Aid for Robert Kalmbach photograph collection, 1960-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Non-Athletic Photos
  - Negatives and Contact Sheets
    - Family and Miscellaneous circa 1957-1974
      - Family, Kids fishing in Huron River (Box 61)
      - Family, Kids swimming at Silver Lake (Box 61)
      - Family, Kim about 1 year old (Box 61)
      - Family, Kim in swimming pool, also boats on lake (Box 61)
      - Family, Kim on rocking horse (Box 61)
      - Family, Rusty and Chryle, 4x5 color transparencies (Box 61)
      - Family, Rusty Birthday party and Doug and Rusty swimming in pool 1965 (Box 61)
      - Family, Ruth and Aubrey, vacation 1973 (Box 61)
      - Family, Skating and sledding at Vets Park January 1970 (Box 61)
      - Family, Skating at Lake Columbia January 1970 (Box 61)
      - Family, Verne and family (Box 61)
        (Flo's negatives)
      - FamilyB, Kids, Easter-time (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Chryle and Terri, Birthday 1963 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Chryle swimming, Smith family swim at Vernes 1964 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Chryle, Mary, and Kim eating, Kim at fish bowl (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Christmas 1966 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Christmas 1966 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Flo and Kim and Chryle;s birthday May, 1964 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kids outside in snow February, 1966 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kids playing and swimming (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kids, Easter-time (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kim's Birthday 1966 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kim's Birthday 1969 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kim's Birthday February 1966 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kim's Birthday February 1966 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kim's birthday February 1967 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kim's first birthday party (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Kim, Rusty, Keith, Thanksgiving 1967 (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Rusty-Hill Auditorium (Box 61)
      - FamilyB, Swimming, Mrs. Smith vacationing July 1961 (Box 61)
      - FamilyC ? School picture 1961, 4x5 negs (Box 61)
      - FamilyC Christmas undated, 4x5 negs (Box 61)
      - FamilyC Family shots and kids 1956, 4x5 negs (Box 61)
      - FamilyC Terri school picture 1966, 4x5 negs (Box 61)
      - FamilyC unidentified family and kids shots, 2x2.5 color negs (Box 61)
      - FamilyC unidentified family shots, 2 folders 4x5 (Box 61)
      - Farm, Cow Scenes, Hanks farm March 1970 (Box 60)
      - Farm House Scene, Kodalith (Box 60)
        (cont. tone neg. filed with "tree on Silver Lake)
      - Farm Scene, Saginaw Forest 1970 (Box 60)
      - Farmers Market (candids of people, old man and old woman) (Box 60)
      - Fishing Trip, Lake Leelanau 1971 (Box 60)
      - Fountain at Music School 1970 (Box 60)
      - Geese, Saginaw forest 1970 (Box 60)
      - Graveyard (Box 60)
      - Great Figures in Jazz (Box 60)
        (copy negatives, appear to be mostly form publications)
      - Hippopotamus, Birmingham, Ala. Zoo 1971, color neg (Box 60)
      - Hood Party, TC (cat) head in window (Box 60)
      - Horses, Kodalith (Box 60)
      - Hunt and Fish Club (night shots of campground lit up and Karl Horning and Art on bicycle August 1970 (Box 60)
      - Hunt and Fish Club picnic January 1970 (Box 60)
      - Huron River, 5x7 color transparencies (Box 60)
      - Huron River, flooding, trees, reflections and water flow shots February, 1971 (Box 60)
      - Huron River, Debris scene, (logs, can, etc.), color (Box 60)
      - Huron River, fog and snow shots and geese March, 1970 (Box 60)
      - Huron River, reflection scene, also kids at home, Margaret Storey and Spring '69 (Box 60)
      - Huron River, snow scenes, trees, Jan 1971 (Box 60)
        (also snow scene on Zeeb Rd.)
      - Huron Tower (Box 60)
      - Kalmbach, Ken, confirmation portraits, 4x5 negs (Box 60)
      - Kalmbach, Tommy (confirmation? / graduation?), 4x5 negs (Box 60)
      - Katy, vacation in Pennsylvania 1967 (Box 60)
      - Kim's negatives, Huron River and Hunt and Fish Club shot (Box 60)
      - Kim's negatives, Alabama and home 1969-1970 (Box 60)
      - Kim's pictures, Snoopy, GiGi and shots around the house (Box 60)
      - Kim playing ball (Box 60)
      - Koch family group shot at Walts 1970 (Box 60)
      - Laura, portraits, 4x5 negs (Box 60)
      - Law Quad spires, Kodalith and color slide (Box 60)
      - Lion, at zoo (Box 60)
      - McNaughtons, Orpha and Bob, family May 1965, 2x2.25 negs. (Box 60)
      - Mental Health Isolation November 16, 1961 (Box 60)
        (patient and sensory deprivation apparatus)
      - Michigras Parade, ladies feet (Box 60)
      - Milahokia Lake, (infrared of trees, outdoor scenes) (Box 60)
      - Miscellaneous August 30, 1970 Rusty water-skiing, Kim and Marcums, outdoor shots (Box 60)
      - Moon shot, moon in middle of deep blue sky, color (Box 60)
      - Mt. Sinai composite (Box 60)
      - Myrtle and Donald vacation July 1966 (Box 60)
      - Nufer family portraits, 1 folders 4x5 (Box 60)
      - Old Postmarks on letters addressed to Lucius Lyon, 4x5 color negs and contact prints (Box 60)
      - Outhouse at Fresh Air Camp, 2 5x7 negs (Box 60)
      - Owl (studio shots), John Turner January 1970 (Box 60)
      - Owl photo (Box 60)
        (studio photos)
      - Pollution Pictures Boy with globe (Box 60)
      - Raccoon in garbage can, hot-air balloon Gerstlers canoeing and scenes at Hunt and Fish Club (Box 60)
      - Real Estate group 1960 (Box 60)
      - Reel Estate group 1960 (Box 60)
      - Rodeo 1967 (Box 60)
      - Rodeo 1966 (Box 60)
      - Rodeo, first rodeo (Box 60)
      - Rodeo, Saline Rodeo 1969 (Box 60)
      - Rodeo, Saline Rodeo 1970 (Box 60)
      - Rodeo undated (Box 60)
      - Rusty's Negs., Huron River and Hunt and Fish Club shots (Box 60)
      - Rusty, Baseball game 1970 (Box 60)
      - Rusty, confirmation 1970 (Box 60)
      - School of Music, construction scene, 5x7 negs (Box 60)
      - Sheree Renee (?) (Box 60)
      - Sky scene, in color form infrared camera (Box 60)
      - Smith, Bill, portrait, 2.2.25 negs (Box 60)
      - Smith, Mrs., and Sis visit (Box 60)
      - Snow Scene, Botanical Garden 1971 (Box 60)
      - Squirrel, snow scenes, color (Box 60)
      - Storey family portrait, 4x5 negs and 35mm (Box 60)
      - Storey, Al, commencement 1972 snow Scenes, January 1967 (Box 60)
      - Sunrise, Milahokia Lake, 2 4x5 color negs. (Box 60)
      - Swamp shots, Silver Lake 1970 (Box 60)
        (piece of wood sticking from water, rain drop in water)
      - Swimming pool (Kim Marcums and Teeters) 1971 (Box 60)
      - Tahquemenon Falls 1959-1960, 4 4x7 negs (Box 60)
      - Tahquemenon Falls 1969, 2x2.25 negs (Box 60)
      - Tahquemenon River, foam (Box 60)
      - Tip-up Town 1968 (Box 60)
      - Tip-Up Town, ice fishermen 1970 (Box 60)
      - Tree (Box 60)
      - Tree and farm shot at Silver Lake (Box 60)
      - Water-skiing, Silver Lake, Rusty and Tom Kennedy July 1974 (Box 60)
      - Weather Vane, Greenfield Village, 4x5 neg (Box 60)
    - Family circa 1956-1957
      (Negatives only. Each entry below represents on roll of 16mm film, titles are from note accompanying boxes of 16mm canisters.)
      - [1] Picture at home September 3, 1956 (Box 61)
      - [2] Rusty Baptized October 10, 1956 (Box 61)
      - [3] Pictures at Hank and Verne's April 1956 (Box 61)
      - [4] Flo's Shower at Verne, Grandma Koch (Box 61)
      - [5] Chryle is 1 year old, May, 8 1956 (Box 61)
      - [6] Erb's resort July 1956 (Box 61)
      - [7] Hank and Verne at Willow Village October 1956 (Box 61)
      - [8] Picture of Chryle 1 week old October 1956 (Box 61)
      - [9] Chryle baptized (Box 61)
      - [10] Pictures at Erb's August 3, 1956 (Box 61)
      - [11] Christmas 1955 (Box 61)
      - [12] Alabama 1955 (Box 61)
      - [13] Pictures at home, Rays, Vernes January 1956 (Box 61)
      - [14] Mother's Day at Walts, May 17. 1956 (Box 61)
      - [15] Halloween 1956 (Box 61)
      - [16] Halloween 1956 (Box 61)
      - [17] Thanksgiving 1956 (Box 61)
      - [18] Christmas 1956 (Box 61)
      - [19] Easter 1957 (Box 61)
      - [20] Alabama June 1957 (Box 61)
      - [21] Alabama 1921 (Box 61)
      - [22] Pictures around home July 1957 (Box 61)
      - [24] Terri, Easter 1958 (Box 61)
      - [25] Rusty and Chryle, early 1957 (Box 61)
      - [26] Ada, Roger in snow January 1958 (Box 61)
      - [27] Pictures of the West (copy negs.) (Box 61)
      - [28] Dad's birthday 1958 (Box 61)
      - [29] Detroit Zoo trip 1958 (Box 61)
      - [30] Detroit Zoo trip 1958 (Box 61)
      - [31] Portraits of Chryle, Rusty, Daddy and Mommy (Box 61)
      - [32] Pictures at home 1958 (Box 61)
      - [33] Terri baptized 1958 (Box 61)
      - [34] Pictures on Packard (Box 61)
      - [35] Peach Festival 1955 (Box 61)
      - [36] Snow scene 1958 (Box 61)
      - [37] Snow scene 1958 (Box 61)
      - [38] Verne's birthday 1956 (Box 61)
- Prints
  - Campus Buildings and Events (Box 60)
  - Performers and Artists (Box 60)
  - Gerald Ford (Box 60)
  - Joseph Brodsky (Box 60)
  - Old German Restaurant Fire (Box 60)
  - Dance Studio (Box 60)
  - Nature Photos (Box 60)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives and Contact Sheets (Box 60)
- Prints (outsize)
  - Sports
    - Football (Box 62)
    - Basketball (Box 62)
    - Football Picture day August 1996 (Box 62)
    - Hockey Aaron Ward and Mike Knuble with Stanley Cup in hockey locker room September 26, 1998 (Box 62)
    - Other Sports (Box 62)
  - Other Topics
    - Performers and Artists (Box 62)
    - Portraits (Box 62)
    - UM Campus (Box 62)
    - Nature (Box 62)
- Digital Images Files
  - Women's Basketball 2000/01, 2 optical disks CDs (Box 60)
    (game action)
  - Water Polo 2000/01, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 60)
    (head shots)